Guide to the Meyer Lissner Papers, 1903-1923 (inclusive), 1910-1920 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. Correspondence In, 1903-1923.
  - How (Box 17, Folder 349)
  - Hub-Hum (Box 17, Folder 350)
  - Hun (Box 17, Folder 351)
  - Hur-Hut (Box 17, Folder 352)
  - I (Box 17, Folder 353)
  - Ickes, H. L. (Box 17, Folder 354)
  - Ja (Box 17, Folder 355)
  - Je (Box 18, Folder 356)
  - Joe-Jones, G. W. (Box 18, Folder 357)
  - Johnson, G. H. (Box 18, Folder 358)
  - Johnson, H. #11910-June 1911 (Box 18, Folder 359)
  - Johnson, H. #2July-December 1911 (Box 18, Folder 360)
  - Johnson, H. #3January-April 1912 (Box 18, Folder 361)
  - Johnson, H. #4May-October 1912 (Box 18, Folder 362)
  - Johnson, H. #5November-December 1912 (Box 18, Folder 363)
  - Johnson, H. #6January-July 1913 (Box 18, Folder 364)
  - Johnson, H. #7November-December 1913 (Box 18, Folder 365)
  - Johnson, H. #8January 1914 (Box 18, Folder 366)
  - Johnson, H. #9February-June 1914 (Box 18, Folder 367)
  - Johnson, H. #10July-December 1914 (Box 18, Folder 368)
  - Johnson, H. #11January-May 1915 (Box 18, Folder 369)
  - Johnson, H. #12June-August 1915 (Box 18, Folder 370)
  - Johnson, H. #13September-December 1915 (Box 18, Folder 371)
  - Johnson, H. #14January-February 1916 (Box 18, Folder 372)
  - Johnson, H. #15March-August 1916 (Box 18, Folder 373)
  - Johnson, H. #16September-December 1916 (Box 19, Folder 374)
  - Johnson, H. #17January-February 1917 (Box 19, Folder 375)
  - Johnson, H. #18March-april 1917, 1918, July-September 1920 (Box 19, Folder 376)
  - Johnson, H. #19October 1920-February 1921 (Box 19, Folder 377)
  - Johnson, H. Jr. (Box 19, Folder 378)
  - Johnson for Senator Club1916-1918, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 379)
  - Johnston, J. (Box 19, Folder 380)
  - Johnstone, W.A. (Box 19, Folder 381)
  - Jones, S.-Jor (Box 19, Folder 382)
  - Jos-Ju (Box 19, Folder 383)
  - Ka-Kei (Box 19, Folder 384)
  - Kel-Kent (Box 19, Folder 385)
  - Kent, W. (Box 19, Folder 386)
  - Kenz-Ki (Box 19, Folder 387)
  - Ke (Box 19, Folder 388)
  - Kn-Ku (Box 19, Folder 389)
  - La (Box 19, Folder 390)
  - LaFollette (Box 19, Folder 391)
  - Lea-Le (Box 19, Folder 392)
  - Lel-Lez (Box 19, Folder 393)
  - Lewinsohn, J.L. #11951-January 1919 (Box 19, Folder 394)
  - Lewinsohn, J.L. #2February 1919-1921 (Box 19, Folder 395)
  - Lic-Liv (Box 19, Folder 396)
  - Lissner A-W (Box 20, Folder 397)
  - Lissner, H.H. (Box 20, Folder 398)
  - Loc-Low (Box 20, Folder 399)
  - Los Angeles #1 A-C (Box 20, Folder 400)
  - Los Angeles #2 D-I (Box 20, Folder 401)
  - Los Angeles #3 L-Pol (Box 20, Folder 402)
  - Los Angeles #4 Pow-Pu (Box 20, Folder 403)
  - Los Angeles #5 R-Y (Box 20, Folder 404)
  - Los Angeles County (Box 20, Folder 405)
  - Lu-Ly (Box 20, Folder 406)
  - Luce, E.A. #11907-1909 (Box 20, Folder 407)
  - Luce, E.A. #21910-May 1912 (Box 20, Folder 408)
  - Luce, E.A. #3June 1912-1915 (Box 20, Folder 409)
  - Luce, E.A. #41916-1921 (Box 20, Folder 410)
  - Lyons, D.B. (Box 20, Folder 411)
  - Mc & Mac, McA-McC (Box 20, Folder 412)
  - McCabe, A. #11910-June 1915 (Box 20, Folder 413)
  - McCabe, A. #2August 1915-1920 (Box 20, Folder 414)
  - McClatchy, C.K. (Box 20, Folder 415)
  - McCormick, M.1912-1915, 1919 (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - Mc & Mac, McD-McI (Box 20, Folder 417)
  - McK-McL (Box 20, Folder 418)
  - Mc & Mac, McM-McV (Box 21, Folder 419)
  - Mab-Man (Box 21, Folder 420)
  - Madsen, M.C. (Box 21, Folder 421)
  - Mar (Box 21, Folder 422)
  - Mas-May (Box 21, Folder 423)
  - Med-Mer (Box 21, Folder 424)
  - Met-Mil (Box 21, Folder 425)
  - Min-Moo (Box 21, Folder 426)
  - Mor-Mos (Box 21, Folder 427)
  - Mot-Mul (Box 21, Folder 428)
  - Mun-My (Box 21, Folder 429)
  - Municipal Conference of 1913 (Box 21, Folder 430)
  - Municipal League of Los Angeles (Box 21, Folder 431)
  - Myers, L. W. (Box 21, Folder 432)
  - Naf-Nat'l E. (Box 21, Folder 433)
  - Nat'l G.-Nau (Box 21, Folder 434)
  - National Municipal League (Box 21, Folder 435)
  - Nea-New J. (Box 21, Folder 436)
  - Nelles, F.C. #11911-1915 (Box 22, Folder 437)
  - Nelles, F.C. #21916-1920 (Box 22, Folder 438)
  - Newm-Ny (Box 22, Folder 439)
  - Neylan, J.F. #11912-1915 (Box 22, Folder 440)
  - Neylan, J.F. #21916-1917 (Box 22, Folder 441)
  - Neylan, J.F. #31918-1920 (Box 22, Folder 442)
  - Ni-Non (Box 22, Folder 443)
  - Noo-Ny (Box 22, Folder 444)
  - Oa-Oh (Box 22, Folder 445)
  - Oi-O'N (Box 22, Folder 446)
  - Op-Os (Box 22, Folder 447)
  - Ot-Oy (Box 22, Folder 448)
  - Pa (Box 22, Folder 449)
  - Pea-Per (Box 22, Folder 450)
  - Perkins, G.W. #11911-1913 (Box 22, Folder 451)
  - Perkins, G.W. #21914-1915 (Box 22, Folder 452)
  - Perkins, G.W. #31916-1918 (Box 22, Folder 453)
  - Pet-Ph (Box 22, Folder 454)
  - Pi-Pl (Box 22, Folder 455)
  - Pinchot, G. (Box 22, Folder 456)
  - Po (Box 23, Folder 457)
  - Pope, A. U. (Box 23, Folder 458)
  - Pr-Pu (Box 23, Folder 459)
  - Ra-Rei (Box 23, Folder 460)
  - Rem-Rey (Box 23, Folder 461)
  - Rh-Rie (Box 23, Folder 462)
  - Republican California Campaign #1September 30-October 11 1910 (Box 23, Folder 463)
  - Republican California Campaign #2October 12-21 1910 (Box 23, Folder 464)
  - Republican California Campaign #3October 22-31 1910 (Box 23, Folder 465)
  - Republican California Campaign #4November 1-6 1910 (Box 23, Folder 466)
  - Ril-Robe (Box 23, Folder 467)
  - Robi-Roosevelt, T. Dr. (Box 23, Folder 468)
  - Robinson, L.S. #11910-1911 (Box 23, Folder 469)
  - Robinson, L.S. #21912, 1913, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 470)
  - Roosevelt, T. #11910-1914 (Box 23, Folder 471)
  - Roosevelt, T. #21915-1919 (Box 23, Folder 472)
  - Roosevelt (Corp.)-Rot (Box 23, Folder 473)
  - Row-Ry (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Rowan, R. R. and Co. (Box 23, Folder 475)
  - Rowell, C.H. #11907-1911 (Box 24, Folder 476)
  - Rowell, C.H. #21912 (Box 24, Folder 477)
  - Rowell, C.H. #31913 (Box 24, Folder 478)
  - Rowell, C.H. #41914 (Box 24, Folder 479)
  - Rowell, C.H. #51915 (Box 24, Folder 480)
  - Rowell, C.H. #61916 (Box 24, Folder 481)
  - Rowell, C.H. #71917 (Box 24, Folder 482)
  - Rowell, C.H. #81918 (Box 24, Folder 483)
  - Rowell, C.H. #91919 (Box 24, Folder 484)
  - Rowell, C.H. #101920 (Box 24, Folder 485)
  - Rowell, C.H. #111921 (Box 24, Folder 486)
  - Sac-San J. (Box 24, Folder 487)
  - San L.-Sav (Box 24, Folder 488)
  - Sc (Box 24, Folder 489)
  - Se (Box 24, Folder 490)
  - Sha-Shi (Box 24, Folder 491)
  - Sho-Shu (Box 24, Folder 492)
  - Sib-Simo (Box 24, Folder 493)
  - Simp-Sis (Box 24, Folder 494)
  - Sl-Sn (Box 24, Folder 495)
  - So (Box 24, Folder 496)
  - Sp-Sta (Box 25, Folder 497)
  - State Compensation Ins. Fund (Box 25, Folder 498)
  - Ste (Box 25, Folder 499)
  - Stephens, W.D. #11911-1916 (Box 25, Folder 500)
  - Stephens, W.D. #21917-1919 (Box 25, Folder 501)
  - Stetson, J.W. (Box 25, Folder 502)
  - Sti-Sto (Box 25, Folder 503)
  - Str-Sun (Box 25, Folder 504)
  - Sur-Sy (Box 25, Folder 505)
  - Ta (Box 25, Folder 506)
  - Te-Thi (Box 25, Folder 507)
  - Tho-Ti (Box 25, Folder 508)
  - Title Insurance and Trust Co. (Box 25, Folder 509)
  - To (Box 25, Folder 510)
  - Tr-Ty (Box 25, Folder 511)
  - U (Box 25, Folder 512)
  - Uhl, Adolph (Box 25, Folder 513)
  - Unknown (Unidentified and Fragments) (Box 25, Folder 514)
  - U'Ren, M.T. (Box 25, Folder 515)
  - V (Box 25, Folder 516)
  - Wad-Was (Box 25, Folder 517)
  - Wallace, A.J. (Box 26, Folder 518)
  - Wat-Web (Box 26, Folder 519)
  - Wei-Wer (Box 26, Folder 520)
  - Weinstock, H. (Box 26, Folder 521)
  - Wes-Wey (Box 26, Folder 522)
  - Whe (Box 26, Folder 523)
  - Whif-White (Box 26, Folder 524)
  - White-Wile (Box 26, Folder 525)
  - White, W.A. (Box 26, Folder 526)
  - Wilk-Will, A.P. (Box 26, Folder 527)
  - Willard, C.D. #1[1907-1911] (Box 26, Folder 528)
  - Willard, C.D. #2[1912-1913] (Box 26, Folder 529)
  - Willard, M.-Williams, W.E. (Box 26, Folder 530)
  - Williams, W.R.-Wilt (Box 26, Folder 531)
  - Win-Woodi (Box 26, Folder 532)
  - Woodley, F.E.-Workin (Box 26, Folder 533)
  - Woodruff, C.R. #11908-1911 (Box 26, Folder 534)
  - Woodruff, C.R. #2January-April 1912 (Box 26, Folder 535)
  - Woodruff, C.R. #3May-July 1912 (Box 26, Folder 536)
  - Woodruff, C.R. #4September 1912-1914 (Box 26, Folder 537)
  - Woodruff, C.R. #51915-1916 (Box 26, Folder 538)
  - Woodruff, C.R. #61917-1920 (Box 27, Folder 539)
  - Works, J.D. (Box 27, Folder 540)
  - Works, L.R.-Wy (Box 27, Folder 541)
  - Ya-Z (Box 27, Folder 542)
  - Young, C.C. #11910-1912 (Box 27, Folder 543)
  - Young, C.C. #21913-1915 (Box 27, Folder 544)
  - Young, C.C. #31916-1920 (Box 27, Folder 545)
- Series 3. California Outlook, 1911-1914.
  Arranged alphabetically, both incoming and outgoing correspondence together, and chronologically under each individual entry.
  The neadings used are generally the same as those of the 1936 arrangement and series B of the present arrangement. The outgoing correspondence is largely by will H. Fischer, but A.E. Norris, F.O. Thorn, Lissner, E.C. Rensberger etc. are also represented. The recipients of these letters and authors of the incoming correspondence are, with very few exceptions, represented in series B. There are also three folders of legal agreements, financial papers, reports and lists of advertisers, subscribers etc. following the correspondence.
  - Ab-American City (Box 27, Folder 546)
  - American Civic-Ande (Box 27, Folder 547)
  - Andr-Ay (Box 27, Folder 548)
  - Bak-Ban (Box 27, Folder 549)
  - Bar-Be (Box 27, Folder 550)
  - Bi-Bl (Box 27, Folder 551)
  - Bo (Box 27, Folder 552)
  - Br (Box 27, Folder 553)
  - Bu-By (Box 27, Folder 554)
  - C-Cal (Box 27, Folder 555)
  - California State Institutions A-H (Box 27, Folder 556)
  - California State Institutions I-U (Box 27, Folder 557)
  - Cam-Ce (Box 28, Folder 558)
  - Cha-Che (Box 28, Folder 559)
  - Chi-Cl (Box 28, Folder 560)
  - Cob-Coo (Box 28, Folder 561)
  - Commonwealth Club (Box 28, Folder 562)
  - Cor-Cu (Box 28, Folder 563)
  - Da (Box 28, Folder 564)
  - De (Box 28, Folder 565)
  - Di-Do (Box 28, Folder 566)
  - Dr-Ed (Box 28, Folder 567)
  - Eg-Ew (Box 28, Folder 568)
  - Fa-Fl (Box 28, Folder 569)
  - Fo-Fu (Box 28, Folder 570)
  - Ga-Gl (Box 28, Folder 571)
  - Go-Gw (Box 28, Folder 572)
  - Graupner, A.E. (Box 28, Folder 573)
  - Ha (Box 28, Folder 574)
  - He-Hi (Box 28, Folder 575)
  - Ho (Box 28, Folder 576)
  - Hu-I (Box 28, Folder 577)
  - J (Box 29, Folder 578)
  - K (Box 29, Folder 579)
  - La (Box 29, Folder 580)
  - Le-Lissner (Box 29, Folder 581)
  - Lit-Los Angeles (city) (Box 29, Folder 582)
  - Los Angeles (county)-Ly (Box 29, Folder 583)
  - Mc and Mac (Box 29, Folder 584)
  - Ma (Box 29, Folder 585)
  - Me-Mi (Box 29, Folder 586)
  - Mof-Mos (Box 29, Folder 587)
  - Mot-Nat'l M. (Box 29, Folder 588)
  - Nat'l R. (Box 29, Folder 589)
  - Oa-Old (Box 29, Folder 590)
  - Oli-Ow (Box 29, Folder 591)
  - Pac-Panama (Box 29, Folder 592)
  - Pan American-Pay (Box 29, Folder 593)
  - Pe-Ph (Box 29, Folder 594)
  - Pi-Po (Box 29, Folder 595)
  - Pr-Pu (Box 29, Folder 596)
  - Progressive Party Organization (county, state, national) (Box 29, Folder 597)
  - Ra-Re (Box 29, Folder 598)
  - Ri (Box 30, Folder 599)
  - Rob-Rol (Box 30, Folder 600)
  - Roo-Ry (Box 30, Folder 601)
  - Rowell, C.H. (Box 30, Folder 602)
  - Sa (Box 30, Folder 603)
  - Sc-Se (Box 30, Folder 604)
  - Sh-Sj (Box 30, Folder 605)
  - Sl-Sp (Box 30, Folder 606)
  - Sr-Ste (Box 30, Folder 607)
  - Sti-Str (Box 30, Folder 608)
  - Su-Sw (Box 30, Folder 609)
  - Ta-Tho (Box 30, Folder 610)
  - Thu-Ty (Box 30, Folder 611)
  - U (Box 30, Folder 612)
  - V (Box 30, Folder 613)
  - Wa (Box 30, Folder 614)
  - We (Box 30, Folder 615)
  - Wh (Box 30, Folder 616)
  - Wi (Box 30, Folder 617)
  - Wo-Wy (Box 30, Folder 618)
  - Y-Z (Box 30, Folder 619)
  - Original Subscriptions (Box 31, Folder 620)
  - California Outlook Company. Advertisers, quarterly financial report, subscription agreements, lists of subscribers (Box 31, Folder 621)
  - California Outlook Fund Cash Book (Box 31, Folder 622)
- Series 4. Johnson for President 1920.
  The correspondence is arranged in the same manner as series 3 with special headings for newspaper advertising, New York Headquarters and San Francisco Headquarters. Outgoing correspondence generally originates from the Los Angeles Headquarters. Following the correspondence are lists of clubs, committees, supporters and contributors, circular letters, publicity material pro and con and a few financial papers.
  - A (Box 31, Folder 623)
  - Ba-Bi (Box 31, Folder 624)
  - Bl-Bu (Box 31, Folder 625)
  - Ca-Ce (Box 31, Folder 626)
  - Carnahan, H.L. (Box 31, Folder 627)
  - Ch-Cl (Box 31, Folder 628)
  - Co-Cu (Box 31, Folder 629)
  - Cochran, G.I. (Box 31, Folder 630)
  - D (Box 31, Folder 631)
  - E (Box 31, Folder 632)
  - Fa-Fl (Box 31, Folder 633)
  - Fo-Fr (Box 31, Folder 634)
  - G (Box 31, Folder 635)
  - Ha-He (Box 31, Folder 636)
  - Hi-Hu (Box 31, Folder 637)
  - Hoover, H.--Campaign Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 638)
  - I-J (Box 31, Folder 639)
  - K-La (Box 31, Folder 640)
  - Le-Ly (Box 32, Folder 641)
  - Mc-Mac (Box 32, Folder 642)
  - McClatchy, C.K. (Box 32, Folder 643)
  - Ma-Mon (Box 32, Folder 644)
  - Moo-My (Box 32, Folder 645)
  - N (Box 32, Folder 646)
  - Newspaper Advertising A-Lon (Box 32, Folder 647)
  - Newspaper Advertising Los-Z (Box 32, Folder 648)
  - New York Headquarters (Box 32, Folder 649)
  - O-P (Box 32, Folder 650)
  - R (Box 32, Folder 651)
  - Rowell, C.H. (Box 32, Folder 652)
  - Sa-Sh (Box 32, Folder 653)
  - San Diego Club (Box 32, Folder 654)
  - San Francisco Headquarters (Box 32, Folder 655)
  - Si-Sw (Box 32, Folder 656)
  - T-V (Box 32, Folder 657)
  - Wa-Wi (Box 32, Folder 658)
  - Wo-Z (Box 32, Folder 659)
  - Club and Committee Lists (Box 32, Folder 660)
  - Club and Committee Lists (Box 33, Folder 661)
  - Registered Supporters Lists (Box 33, Folder 662)
  - Registered Supporters Lists Contributors (Box 33, Folder 663)
  - Circular Letters (pro Jonnson) (Box 33, Folder 664)
  - Publicity (pro Johnson) (Box 33, Folder 665)
  - Publicity (pro opposition) (Box 33, Folder 666)
  - Financial (Box 33, Folder 667)
- Series 5. Miscellaneous
  The six folders contain a few clippings, printed calling cards and invitations, formal appointments, membership cards, personal notes, a few legal and financial items etc. filed according to form.
  - Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 33, Folder 668)
  - Memberships and Calling Cards (Box 33, Folder 669)
  - Personal Notes (Box 33, Folder 670)
  - Lissner Appointments (Box 33, Folder 671)
  - Pamphlets and Lists (Box 33, Folder 672)
  - Legal, Financial, Personal Papers (Box 34, Folder 673)
  - Tarbell, Ida. Announcement of series of articles, 1914 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Series 6. Printed Reference Material
  This series consists primarily of newspaper clippings, some news releases, manuscript speeches, form letters and a few legal documents filed alphabetically by subject. Duplicate materials, pamphlets and photographs were removed. The general arrangement remains unchanged. This material is thought to have formed a newspaper morgue for the California Outlook.
  - Adams-Americanization (Box 34, Folder 674)
  - Anderson-Avery (Box 34, Folder 675)
  - Banking-Berkeley (Box 34, Folder 676)
  - Better American Federation of California-Beveridge (Box 34, Folder 677)
  - Birth Control-Brandeis (Box 34, Folder 678)
  - Breed-Bryan (Box 34, Folder 679)
  - Bryant-California Delegation to Republican National Convention (Box 34, Folder 680)
  - California Division of State-Legislation Proposed (Box 34, Folder 681)
  - California Maps-Charter Revision (Box 35, Folder 682)
  - Charters of Cities-City Home Rule (Box 35, Folder 683)
  - City Manager Plan (Box 35, Folder 684)
  - Civic Betterment-Civil Service Problems (Box 35, Folder 685)
  - Cogswell-Commission Plan (Box 35, Folder 686)
  - Commissions-Constitution and State (Box 36, Folder 687)
  - Constitution (U.S.)-Dickson (Box 36, Folder 688)
  - Direct Legislation-Earl (Box 36, Folder 689)
  - Edson-Election Laws (Box 36, Folder 690)
  - Efficiency and Economy (Box 36, Folder 691)
  - Efficiency and Economy (Box 36, Folder 692)
  - Election Laws Nominating Petitions (Box 36, Folder 693)
  - Election Laws Sample Ballots (Box 36, Folder 694)
  - Election Laws Convention System, Referential Voting (Box 37, Folder 695)
  - Election Laws Second Class Voting, Presidential Primary (Box 37, Folder 696)
  - Election Laws Primary Election, Direct Primary (Box 37, Folder 697)
  - Election Laws Direct Primary Laws, Regulation of Public Utilities, Sample Ballot, Short Ballot (Box 37, Folder 698)
  - Election Laws Statistics, U.S. Senators, Voting Compulsary, Voting Machines, Ward System (Box 37, Folder 699)
  - Eshleman-European War (Box 37, Folder 700)
  - Fe-Fo (Box 37, Folder 701)
  - Francis-Frank (Box 37, Folder 702)
  - Fredericks (Box 37, Folder 703)
  - Free-Gibson (Box 37, Folder 704)
  - Gillett-Greenhood (Box 37, Folder 705)
  - Good Government Reports (Box 38, Folder 706)
  - Hamilton-Hays (Box 38, Folder 707)
  - Hearst-Heney (Box 38, Folder 708)
  - Hetch-Hughes (Box 38, Folder 709)
  - Immigration-Indiana (Box 38, Folder 710)
  - Insurance-Johnson, G. (Box 38, Folder 711)
  - Johnson, H. (Box 39, Folder 712)
  - Johnson, H. (Box 39, Folder 713)
  - Johnson, H. (Box 39, Folder 714)
  - Jordan-Knowland (Box 39, Folder 715)
  - Labor-LaBrea (Box 39, Folder 716)
  - LaFollette (Box 40, Folder 717)
  - League of Nations (Box 40, Folder 718)
  - League fro Preservation of American Independence-Lindsey (Box 40, Folder 719)
  - Lincoln-Roosevelt League (Box 40, Folder 720)
    Includes: Documents of Records of State Emigration, Documents and Records of L.A. County Organization, News Clippings, Campaign Literature -- Forms
  - Lissner Speeches (Box 40, Folder 721)
  - Lissner Speeches (Box 40, Folder 722)
  - Lissner Documents, Clippings, Articles (Box 40, Folder 723)
  - Lloyd George-Lodge (Box 41, Folder 724)
  - Los Angeles Aquaduct (Box 41, Folder 725)
  - Los Angeles Bar Association-Charter Amendment (Box 41, Folder 726)
  - Los Angeles Charter Amendment and Conference (Box 41, Folder 727)
  - Los Angeles Charter Information (Box 41, Folder 728)
  - Los Angeles Charter Committees (Box 41, Folder 729)
  - Los Angeles Charter Reform-City [Arnold] Plan (Box 41, Folder 730)
  - Los Angeles City [Robinson] Plan-City Planning (Box 42, Folder 731)
  - Los Angeles City Statistics-Consolidation (Box 42, Folder 732)
  - Los Angeles Efficiency Bureau-Franchises (Box 42, Folder 733)
  - Los Angeles Freeholders Board of (Box 42, Folder 734)
  - Los Angeles Freeholders Board of (Box 42, Folder 735)
  - Los Angeles Fire Departments-Harbor (Box 42, Folder 736)
  - Los Angeles Liquor Ordinance-Maps (Box 42, Folder 737)
  - Los Angeles Mercantile Place-Municipal Newspaper Ordinance (Box 43, Folder 738)
  - Los Angeles Parcel Post-Public Library (Box 43, Folder 739)
  - Los Angeles Schools-Union Depot (Box 43, Folder 740)
  - Los Angeles County Civil Service Board-Superior Court (Box 43, Folder 741)
  - Lowden-Moore (Box 43, Folder 742)
  - McNamara Case (Box 43, Folder 743)
  - Mothers' Pension-Mulholland (Box 43, Folder 744)
  - Municipal Conference (Box 44, Folder 745)
  - Municipal Conference (Box 44, Folder 746)
  - Municipal Research-Neylen/Stephen Controversy (Box 44, Folder 747)
  - Non Partisan Bill-Non Partisan Legislature (Box 44, Folder 748)
  - Non Partisanship (Box 44, Folder 749)
  - Norton-Otis (Box 44, Folder 750)
  - Panama Canal (Box 44, Folder 751)
  - Pasadena-Pinchot (Box 45, Folder 752)
  - Platform (Box 45, Folder 753)
  - Platform-Political Boss (Box 45, Folder 754)
  - Political Campaigns Republican Convention of 1908-Recall of 1909 (Box 45, Folder 755)
  - Political Campaigns Municipal of 1911-Republican of 1912 (Box 45, Folder 756)
  - Political Campaigns Non Partisan Campaign of 1915 (Box 45, Folder 757)
  - Political Campaigns Non Partisan Campaign of 1915 (Box 45, Folder 758)
  - Political Campaigns Presidential Primary of 1912 (Box 46, Folder 759)
  - Political Campaigns Presidential Primary of 1912 (Box 46, Folder 760)
  - Political Campaigns Court Contest of 1912-Municipal Election of 1915 (Box 46, Folder 761)
  - Political Campaigns Presidential Campaign of 1916-Presidential Primary of 1920 (Box 46, Folder 762)
  - Political Campaigns Republican Election of 1920-Primary of 1922 (Box 46, Folder 763)
  - Poll Tax-Progressive Party (Box 46, Folder 764)
  - Progressive Party (National)-Progressive and Republican Compromise of 1916 (Box 46, Folder 765)
  - Progressive Republican League of California-Prohibition (Box 47, Folder 766)
  - Proportional Representation (Box 47, Folder 767)
  - Proportional Representation (Box 47, Folder 768)
  - Public Ownership-Reappointment (Box 47, Folder 769)
  - Recall of Judiciary-Republican State Central Committee (Box 47, Folder 770)
  - Richardson-Rominger (Box 47, Folder 771)
  - Roosevelt (Box 47, Folder 772)
  - Roosevelt (Box 47, Folder 773)
  - Roosevelt (Box 48, Folder 774)
  - Roosevelt-Roosevelt Memorial (Box 48, Folder 775)
  - Root-Rural Credits (Box 48, Folder 776)
  - San Diego-San Francisco Waterfront (Box 48, Folder 777)
  - San Pedro Harbor-Sierra Club (Box 48, Folder 778)
  - Single Tax (Box 48, Folder 779)
  - Sloane-Spalding (Box 49, Folder 780)
  - Spellacy-Statute Law (Box 49, Folder 781)
  - Stephens-Survey Associates (Box 49, Folder 782)
  - Taft-Tariff Commission (Box 49, Folder 783)
  - Taxation-Torrens Land Act (Box 49, Folder 784)
  - Tree Planting (Box 49, Folder 785)
  - Trusts and Monopolies-U.S. Shipping Board (Box 49, Folder 786)
  - U.S. Shipping Board (Box 49, Folder 787)
  - Underwood-Usury Bill (Box 50, Folder 788)
  - Vaccination-Watt (Box 50, Folder 789)
  - Weinstock-Wilson (Box 50, Folder 790)
  - Wilson (Box 50, Folder 791)
  - Woman Suffrage (Box 50, Folder 792)
  - Woodley-Works (Box 50, Folder 793)
  - YMCA-Young (Box 50, Folder 794)
- Series 7. Lissner Clippings, 1907-1916.
  These mounted clippings are arranged chronologically and relate to Lissner and various topics and persons in whom he was interested. Some of these he collected, but most were supplied by Allen's Bureau.
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, January 4 1907-March 5 1909 (Box 50, Folder 795)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, March 20-June 30 1909 (Box 51, Folder 796)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, July 22 1909-February 22 1910 (Box 51, Folder 797)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, March 5-April 22 1910 (Box 51, Folder 798)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, May 1-31 1910 (Box 51, Folder 799)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, June 1-30 1910 (Box 51, Folder 800)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, July 1-31 1910 (Box 51, Folder 801)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, August 1-31 1910 (Box 52, Folder 802)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, September 1910 (Box 52, Folder 803)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, September 1910 (Box 52, Folder 804)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, September 7-October 6 1910 (Box 52, Folder 805)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, October 7-October 14 1910 (Box 52, Folder 806)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, October 14-15 1910 (Box 52, Folder 807)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, October 15-20 1910 (Box 53, Folder 808)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, October 21-25 1910 (Box 53, Folder 809)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, October 25-29 1910 (Box 53, Folder 810)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, October 29-November 5 1910 (Box 53, Folder 811)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, November 5-11 1910 (Box 53, Folder 812)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, November 13-17 1910 (Box 53, Folder 813)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, November 17-18 1910 (Box 53, Folder 814)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, November 18-20 1910 (Box 54, Folder 815)
  - Clippings re: Meyer Lissner, November 21 1910-February 14 1916 (Box 54, Folder 816)
- Series 8. Pamphlets